Let's go ahead and write out the constructor function called SoftwareDeveloper.
我们编写叫做 SoftwareDeveloper 的构造函数
So just to recap, when SoftwareDeveloper is invoked with the new keyword,
总结下 如果使用关键字 new 调用 SoftwareDeveloper
it's going to create a new object that has a favorite language property,
将创建一个新的对象 其中具有 favoriteLanguage 属性
has a value of JavaScript.
值为 JavaScript
Now let's go ahead and call
我们使用关键字 new
the SoftwareDeveloper constructor function with a new keyword, and create a new object.
调用构造函数 SoftwareDeveloper 并新建一个对象
Let's call it developer.
称之为 developer
If we check out what developer looks like,
看看 developer 的样子
we can see that it's indeed an object over here with a single property favorite language,
它的确是一个对象 具有一个属性 favoriteLanguage
points to a string JavaScript.
设为字符串 JavaScript
And what's really nice is that we can also see
最方便的是还可以看到
the constructor function SoftwareDeveloper,
在 Chrome 开发者工具中
referenced over here in Chrome DevTools as well.
还引用了构造函数 SoftwareDeveloper
Now, instead of calling
现在我们手动写一个新的对象
the software developer constructor function to create a new object,
而不是调用 SoftwareDeveloper 构造函数
let's write one out manually.
创建一个
Let's write it out with object literal notation.
我们采用对象字面量的方式手动编写
We'll call this one otherDeveloper.
称之为 otherDeveloper
Great, and let's access it just for good measure.
访问它 看看效果
So compared to developer,
与 developer 相比
itsSeems like the object looks pretty much the same actually.
这两个对象看起来似乎一样
Again, it's a single property pointing to a JavaScript just like over here.
它同样具有一个属性 值为 JavaScript 和这里一样
But notice that the constructor function that we
但注意创建对象所用的构造函数
created it with isn't listed in Chrome DevTools.
没有列在 Chrome 开发者工具中
It might look different depending on if you're using let's say Safari DevTools,
根据你所使用的开发者工具（例如 Safari 开发者工具或 Firefox 中的开发者工具）
or maybe something in Firefox,
看起来可能不一样
but in Chrome, usually shows the constructor function that created it right over here.
但在 Chrome 中 创建对象用到的构造函数通常会显示在这里
Let's open up each of these.
展开每个部分
And now check out their proto properties.
看看它们的 proto 属性
Don't worry too much about what proto is for now.
暂时不用担心什么是 proto
We'll take a deep dive into it a little bit later.
稍后我们会详细讲解的
So you can see that the constructor for
可以看出 developer 的构造函数
the developer object was actually the software developer constructor function,
实际上是 SoftwareDeveloper 函数
but in the case of other developer,
但是对于 otherDeveloper
the constructor property actually points to the object constructor.
constructor 属性实际上为 object 构造函数
So just a quick comparison.
快速比较下
The prototypes are going to be a little bit different.
原型将有所不同
We'll take a deeper dive into each of these shortly.
稍后我们会详细讲解每个原型的